Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
The Tobi Roppo and the Lead Performers.
The allied armies led by the Straw Hats
eliminated them all.
However, they're cornered by
the formidable Emperors of the Sea!
Bring it on,
shitheads of the Worst Generation!
Luffy vs. Kaido!
The fierce fight speeds up!
I'm sick of hearing Gum-Gum!
Roc Gun!
It's getting fun!
I feel the same!
"Drunken Dragon Bagua!
The Lawless Dragon Closing in on Luffy"
The clash is so intense...
Onigashima is shaking!
I can do it!
I am sure I can!
Onigashima...
...will be stopped
by me, Kozuki Momonosuke!
FLOWER CAPITAL, LAND OF WANO
That hit the spot!
Limit yourself.
You're drinking too much!
Idiot! It's the only day of the year
we get to drink!
You're right.
Other than that,
living in this country is miserable...
Hey, Orochi!
--You wastrel lord...
--Hey, stop it!
Public officials can be anywhere...
Don't worry about such a thing today.
Look.
They started preparing Sky Ships...
The festival is coming to an end.
There are so many lanterns!
HOPE I CAN FEED MY CHILDREN EVERY DAY
I WANT TO SEE MY MOM
Write down your wish
to your deceased ancestors.
What should I wish for?
Why don't you write your wish, too?
Will my wish come true?
Yes.
Your ancestors in heaven
will find the floating Sky Ship,
and make your wish come true.
Will Daddy read it?
Of course, he will.
My wish...
Oh, yeah!
I wanna be able to
make people laugh more!
That's a good one!
Uh-huh! I wanna be like Dad!
Someone who can cheer everyone up!
So, I wanna become
a good dancer like Dad.
And...
I wrote down my wish!
Let's see...
I WANNA SEE YOU, DAD
I wanna be like Dad,
but more than anything,
I wanna see him!
Dad will find my Sky Ship, right?
And my wish will come true.
I think so.
I'm sure your Sky Ship
will look more dazzling...
...to Yasuie-dono than anything else...
It's a nice night.
A full moon in the sky.
An enemy on the earth.
They're both superb.
There aren't many nights like this.
Why are you drinking booze now?!
Because I'm having fun.
Be serious! We're not playing around!
It's the Fire Festival today
in the capital.
We were supposed to have a big banquet
on Onigashima, too.
But you guys messed it all up...
Do you want some?
I don't really like to drink!
What are you, a kid?
Let's have a great time together.
I won't have one with you.
After I take you down,
I'll have a nice big banquet with everyone!
Sounds like fun!
I hope you can have that nice big banquet!
Looks like you're feeling good.
Are you drunk?!
As if I'd get drunk
from just this amount of booze!
My big banquet...
How dare you mess up my banquet!
Straw Hat!
You are drunk!
If you're gonna drink,
why not let loose?
Straw Hat!
What are you doing?!
Can you really fight like that?!
Even if you lose,
don't use an excuse like "I was drunk"!
You idiot!
Why would I wanna make myself weak?
I've accepted you!
Gum-Gum...
Drunken Dragon Bagua!
DRUNKEN DRAGON BAGUA
What?!
I'm feeling good!
When was the last time I met someone
who could really go toe-to-toe with me?
Lightning Hammered!
LIGHTNING HAMMERED
Ragnaraku!
This place is no longer of use...
The island is all screwed up...
It's fun, but at the same time,
the castle is half destroyed.
Damn... I can't even save my castle...
I think now I'm not so...
I'm not so...
We gotta rebuild...
It took five years to build it!
DROWNING HIS SORROWS
That hurt!
That bastard!
Damn...
Are you really drunk?!
I sold weapons here and there,
and even formed
the world's strongest army with Smiles...
I did my best!
I lowered my guard! I'm so dumb!
But maybe I can't do this anymore...
I've been trying so hard...
Why...
Why is this happening to me?!
Gum-Gum...!
I want everything to be destroyed!
Dragon Twister Demolition Breath!
He's flailing around as he pleases!
Leave me alone!
What are you talking about?!
It's a shame and regretful!
I'm doomed! I... I...
Leave me alone!
You fool!
TEARS IN HIS BEER
It's too late for you to whine!
If you don't leave me alone, take this!
I'll shatter everything into pieces!
Why's everything so annoying?!
My son ran away...
He even attacked his parent...
Damn! Nothing goes right!
This is so unfair!
It's hard to stay focused...
It's all...
...your fault!
What?!
LIGHTNING HAMMERED
Isn't it fun to struggle
over life and death?
Dance with me some more!
How could you challenge me
again and again?!
Straw Hat! I think you like me too much!
Thunder...
...Bagua!
Take this, you drunk ass!
His Haki is getting stronger!
It's fun to be drunk...
Stop trying to sober me up!
DRUNKEN RAGE
Be more creative!
It's not entertaining at all!
Make it more exciting!
Gum-Gum...
Kundali...
Roc Gatling!
Dragon Swarm!
SACRED MARIJOA, RED LINE
This year's Reverie is cursed.
The total abolition of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
The incident concerning
the Kingdom of Alabasta...
The Revolutionary Army's
infiltration of Marijoa...
Leave that aside for now.
THE FIVE ELDERS
HIGHEST AUTHORITIES OF THE WORLD
What we must deal with immediately
is the Land of Wano.
Who would imagine that
the battle would get that intense?
We must do something now.
They must have captured Nico Robin by now.
In a battle against Kaido and Big Mom,
death is to be expected.
Must be erased!
And the existence of
that Devil Fruit as well.
OFF THE COAST OF THE LAND OF WANO
Maintain combat readiness
until further notice.
All ships, remain on standby.
Sir...
What is it?
Well, I see a giant shadow...
A shadow? What is it?
I don't know.
What are you talking about?
A-An island?!
No, that's impossible!
That fruit became a mere legend,
even to us now.
It hasn't awakened for centuries.
Then, why did the World Government...
...bother giving that Devil Fruit
another name?!
To hide its name from history.
Kid and Law are an under all-out attack
from a heavyweight.
Is the ambition to overthrow
the Emperor of the Sea just a youthful mistake?!
Just dreaming about defeating the Emperor of the Sea,
they must pay the price in despair,
but an insistent magnetic force of rebellion
awakens the soul of a beast lying in metal scraps!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Destruction of the Alliance?!
Fire up, the Will of the New Generation!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!